{
	"questions": [
		{
			"question": "Who was Captain of the Griffindor Quidditch team in Harry's first year?",
			"options": [
				"Katie Bell",
				"Alicia Spinnet",
				"Charlie Weasley",
				"Oliver Wood"
			],
			"correctOption": 3,
			"points": 10
		},
		{
			"question": "Who was Captain of the Revenclaw Quidditch team in Harry's third year?",
			"options": [
				"Terry Boot",
				"Roberta Bradley",
				"Marcus Belby",
				"Roger Davies"
			],
			"correctOption": 2,
			"points": 10
		},
		{
			"question": "Who was Captain of the Slytherin Quidditch team in Harry's first year?",
			"options": [
				"Miles Blerchley",
				"Terence Higgs",
				"Adrian Pucey",
				"Marcus Flint"
			],
			"correctOption": 3,
			"points": 10
		},
		{
			"question": "Why did Harry miss the final Quidditch game of the season in Philosopher's Stone?",
			"options": [
				"Because he was in the hospital wing",
				"Because he was in detention with Filch",
				"Because he overslept",
				"Because he'd been sent back to the Dursley's early"
			],
			"correctOption": 0,
			"points": 10
		},
		{
			"question": "Who was commentating at the first match of Harry?",
			"options": [
				"Zacharias Smith",
				"Lee Jordan",
				"Luna Lovegood",
				"Lavander Brown"
			],
			"correctOption": 1,
			"points": 10
		},
		{
			"question": "In which Book did Harry first fly against Ravenclaw Seeker Cho Chang?",
			"options": [
				"Philosopher's Stone",
				"Order of the Phoenix",
				"Chamber of Secrets",
				"Prisoner of Azkaban"
			],
			"correctOption": 3,
			"points": 10
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of Ron's brothers was once a Gryffindor Quidditch captain",
			"options": ["George", "Bill", "Charlie", "Fred"],
			"correctOption": 2,
			"points": 30
		},
		{
			"question": "Who was Gryffindor's team captain when Ron became Keeper",
			"options": [
				"Ginny Weasley",
				"Oliver Wood",
				"Harry Potter",
				"Angelina Johnson"
			],
			"correctOption": 3,
			"points": 20
		},
		{
			"question": "Which Quidditch players score goals?",
			"options": ["Keeper", "Seeker", "Beater", "Chaser"],
			"correctOption": 3,
			"points": 20
		},
		{
			"question": "Which position does Harry Potter play at Hogwarts?",
			"options": ["Centre forward", "Seeker", "Beater", "Chaser"],
			"correctOption": 1,
			"points": 30
		},
		{
			"question": "When a Seeker catches the Golden Snitch, how many points do they win for their team and end the match?",
			"options": ["1 point", "100 points", "5 points", "150 points"],
			"correctOption": 3,
			"points": 30
		},
		{
			"question": "Harry is said to love this particular Quidditch team. Who are they??",
			"options": [
				"Ballycastle Bats",
				"Holyhead Harpies",
				"Caerphilly Catapults",
				"Montrose Magpies"
			],
			"correctOption": 1,
			"points": 10
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of these Gryffindors did NOT try out for the Quidditch team after Harry was made captain?",
			"options": [
				"Demelza Robins",
				"Cormac McLaggen",
				"Jimmy Peakes",
				"Neville Longbottom"
			],
			"correctOption": 3,
			"points": 30
		},
		{
			"question": "In which year did Harry and the Gryffindor team first win the Quidditch House Cup",
			"options": ["Second year", "Third year", "Fifth year", "First year"],
			"correctOption": 1,
			"points": 30
		},
		{
			"question": "How many balls are involved in one game of Quidditch",
			"options": ["Five", "Two", "Four", "Three"],
			"correctOption": 2,
			"points": 20
		}
	]
}
